export const FlashCardData = {
    "1": {
        "name": "1DigitToAll",
        "front": "1",
        "back": "ichi"
    },
    "2": {
        "name": "2DigitToAll",
        "front": "2",
        "back": "ni"
    },
    "3": {
        "name": "3DigitToAll",
        "front": "3",
        "back": "san"
    },
    "4": {
        "name": "4DigitToAll",
        "front": "4",
        "back": "shi(yon)"
    },
    "5": {
        "name": "5DigitToAll",
        "front": "5",
        "back": "go"
    },
    "6": {
        "name": "6DigitToAll",
        "front": "6",
        "back": "roku"
    },
    "7": {
        "name": "7DigitToAll",
        "front": "7",
        "back": "shichi(nana)"
    },
    "8": {
        "name": "8DigitToAll",
        "front": "8",
        "back": "hachi"
    },
    "9": {
        "name": "9DigitToAll",
        "front": "9",
        "back": "ku(kyuu)"
    },
    "10": {
        "name": "10DigitToAll",
        "front": "10",
        "back": "juu"
    }
}